I...
This girl...
I really...
The internet sucks. What a wasteland. People on the internet have no...
Kolgaku?
Yamada's on TV?
Every Tuesday at 7pm?
That's today!
I'm too late.
What's up, bro? Whatcha watching?
What's your deal?
I'm gonna turn this off if you're not watching!
頬色に
茜さす火は柔らかに
弾けた
斜ように
僕らは目も開かぬまま
No, it won't let me again
No way because my hand has been cut
So헛しく t was no August
my途或
SUBJECT 2
僕らは目も分かぬまま
I like Yamada.
That's it, though. Nothing else.
It's not like I want to be her boyfriend or go out with her.
Things are still the same as always.
In fact, things need to stay the same.
I hate these marathon runs.
I don't like them either. Let's run together.
You don't mind?
Nope.
What are they up to?
Yep, I knew it.
After consideration, I've completely changed my mind about crap like the school festival and our workplace visits.
But this?
Wait! A guy like me can't let Yamada beat him?
What are you doing? That was fast. I told you to leave me alone when others are around.
You did?
Okay. That put some distance between...
And now I'm slowing down for some reason.
Don't you have that on back horse?
Oh, you're right. I do.
Hold this for a second.
Oh, God.
Now I've got to slow down again.
I can't believe...
Huh?
Wait. Why'd you...
Your right eye!
What?
I'd never seen it before.
Wait, what?
Huh?
I'm seriously about to die.
And so, I wound up in last place.
Everyone headed back into class already.
I'm sorry I ran off ahead like that.
It's fine. We all need to keep our own pace.
Although, Yamada, you weren't running at your own pace up there at all.
Hara!
That was impressive, though. I couldn't keep up.
Oh, come on.
This is Yamada we're talking about.
There was nothing special about that.
What am I doing letting my thoughts run wild?
Hmm?
Huh?
What?
If I get me a lover boy, I want to switch gym shirts with him!
I'd show up wearing one way too big for me.
Ugh.
You're the one.
Yep.
Yeah, but if you're in the same class, you wouldn't be able to do that.
There's absolutely zero chance I'd date anyone in this class anyway.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
This is bad.
If she gets caught wearing my shirt before she even realizes it...
Huh? Why are you wearing that creepy little freak shirt?
I bet it reeks.
People are going to think really bad of her.
Fourth period is about to start.
If we can just get through this class and lunch, then it'll be recess.
Huh?
But she just put it on!
I guess it is getting chilly.
Maybe I'll...
No, no way!
I'd just be considered a perv if I wore it on purpose.
All right, come up here and solve this one, Arachi.
But...
Oh, sure.
Well, shoot!
He's the last person I won't noticing this.
And the only thing he's ever interested in is boobs.
Huh?
Ichikawa?
Um, teacher, please!
I want to solve this one!
For real?
Very well, then Ichikawa, you come up.
Oh, man, it's as clear as day!
Can I get her to realize somehow?
Come on already!
Hey!
What's your deal, man?
You trying to pose like you're somebody and tell us to leave a problem as easy as this
all to you?
No!
Looking cool out there, Ichikawa!
Hate to break it to you, but I'm afraid that is incorrect.
I want to curl up and die so bad I could murder myself.
But the real mess is only just getting started.
I'm so hungry!
Quit showing your chest!
Here.
Ah!
Right.
Big portions.
Oh.
Let's eat everything!
Ew, I'm totally stuffed!
That's because you ate way too much.
I'm gonna have a heart attack.
Ichikawa!
We made it, somehow.
I wonder when they got swapped.
Y-yeah.
I didn't even notice.
I'm a terrible liar.
Weren't you cold not wearing yours?
I would be freezing if I didn't wear it.
No, not really.
Not now, at least.
But when did she finally notice?
I wonder.
There's a little rye stuck to it.
Let's measure each other!
What?
Why would we-
It'll be fun!
Why's this so hard?
I'll use my hand.
Huh?
I-I'm bigger when I'm up straight.
Now do me, okay?
I'll need a boost.
How rude!
171.9.
Just a bit shy of 172.
Okay.
Now let's measure you again.
We'll do it properly.
Hmm?
No.
Let's just go.
It's not fair we only did me.
You're the one who said you wanted to do it.
You saw that, didn't you?
I did not.
Who even cares how much you weigh, though?
So then, you did see it!
No, I didn't!
You did!
Okay, I did.
But I forgot already.
I can't believe that!
You definitely remember!
Nothing has really changed, even after I realized I like her.
It only makes sense.
She doesn't even know.
What if there's a love scene or something?
Oh, well, that's not a big deal.
I bet it's just some crappy art film.
No way!
Now Kisuga's playing the main character?
Even I've got butterflies flying in my stomach!
Wait!
Even I know that actor!
But what's that got to do with you, Moe?
What do you mean?
We're all one here!
Isn't it crazy it's directed by Kenichi Fukuda, though?
It'll be in theaters all over!
Hmm.
The director from the Cannes Festival?
Even I can tell this sounds like her big break as an actress.
A first step to a major career.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Why doesn't she look happy?
Ah, I see now.
I bet she's feeling a tinge of sorrow for poor folk like us
as she continues to move into the upper echelons of society.
She's always been kind like that.
All right, time for homeroom.
Everyone be seated.
Okay.
As I explained last week, we will be changing our seats today.
So I made cards for you to draw.
I want everyone to come up and get one, starting with the back.
Seat change, huh?
Only the gods can work out this puzzle.
Hurry already!
Where'd you end up?
Looks like we got split up.
Thank goodness.
What's that supposed to mean?
Everyone pick up your desks and move to your new spots.
Gods above.
Oh, gods above.
Gods, please.
Gods...
Be damned.
Guess we're close.
Guess so.
Guess I'm next to you, Yamada.
Guess who he is the god.
Maybe I should be glad about this.
I'm so happy.
So, so happy.
Who's going to wind up next to me then?
Oh, Hara.
Bye.
Hooray.
This might not be so bad.
You're so close.
Might be pretty good even.
Or so I thought.
Hey now.
Why do you keep moving?
Her eyelashes are so long.
Huh?
I wasn't looking at you.
You're just in my line of sight when I look at the board.
Oh no.
I guess I forgot my modern Japanese book.
Oh, here then.
The classic textbook sharing event.
You know, I'm pretty sure you just had it in your desk.
See?
This guy's all over me lately.
I can't ditch him.
Are you in love?
This really is a problem, though.
I can't see the board at all.
Sorry.
You can't see?
Um, no.
If you want to, you can copy from my notes.
Huh?
It might be best if we talk with the teacher later.
Yeah.
Hara's so warm-hearted.
That's working out well.
Huh?
Yara!
What's up?
Don't what's up me.
Why are you coming over here?
You come over here!
Who made you king?
Something wrong with her?
Maybe she doesn't actually want to be in that movie.
Still, I gotta deal with this blackboard situation.
She did seem pretty concerned about her height, though.
I can't just tell her,
You're so huge, I can't see the board!
You must like it, sitting next to Hara.
What?
Not really.
She's so nice and pleasant to be around.
Cute, too.
You know, during class...
Huh?
All I see is you.
So I have a really hard time seeing the...
I just went and talked with the teacher.
Huh?
Oh.
So he just couldn't see the board, then.
Uh-huh.
But that's all taken care of now.
Why's it gotta be like this?
In the worst way possible, but...
Sorry.
No.
I know you...
Have plenty to worry about already.
Hm?
What exactly?
Huh?
You know, like...
That big movie and stuff?
Hm?
Are you into watching movies, Ishikawa?
It's like she was waiting for me to bring it up.
Um, so you're gonna be in one with a real director?
Yep.
Sure am.
Playing a tree?
What?
Be for real.
I play the daughter of the police officer who's after the lead guy.
And it's a real role, too.
Oh.
Is that all?
She's a high school student, and her police officer dad dies partway through it, but...
Wait.
She seems way more excited than earlier.
Was it because...
No one bothered to ask her about her part?
I even have a real line!
Huh.
Ahem.
You're such a creep.
Huh?
That's my whole big line.
Uh-oh.
Big line, huh?
I don't usually talk like that, so I need to practice.
Ugh.
You're such a creep.
You should sound even more serious.
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
You're such a creep.
That's even better.
You're getting better and better.
Wow.
Wait.
Hang on.
We should really go somewhere that's less crowded.
She's dangerous.
For what you need, isn't this a little too private?
It's not like there's anywhere else we can go.
Maybe.
But this is pretty cramped for the two of us.
Mm-hmm.
So, well, uh, when's the movie actually coming out?
We start filming relatively soon.
Maybe springtime two years from now?
That's a long ways off.
That's just how it goes.
Spring two years from now.
So, by then, will me and her still be together?
Will you go see it?
I don't know.
What?
But I'll see what all I can manage.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'll see if I can go see it.
Then we're done.
Huh?
What about practicing your lines?
I can't say that.
Discovery Columbus Gakuin!
Huh?
Here goes.
Here we are, everyone.
It's Discovery Columbus Gakuin!
What?
Where is she?
We're trying high school students to hear what the youth of today have to say.
Should prove everything...
There she is!
Here's our topic for the day.
She's wearing a sailor uniform.
Let's talk about Shumai.
Do you like Shumai, Mai Mai?
I love Shumai!
Mai Mai, yes, I do!
Was that it?
Guess it's hard to get air time with so many people.
Terrific.
Now then, let's hear from Miku.
Oh!
Does anyone really want apricot placed in their lunchbox?
What?
Of course they do!
Look at her, looking at her!
She's gonna say something!
All right, students.
Thanks for answering.
We've got all your opinions in.
What?
Don't tell me.
Well, there you have it, folks.
She's on again!
Right out of the mouths of the kids themselves.
No, wait.
I wouldn't believe it if I heard it myself.
But now you know...
This probably happens all the time.
This is how the youth of today really...
She's really only on when she's staring at someone too much.
Or laughing at the comedian's really unfunny jokes.
Or when she doesn't fit in her box.
Be sure to tune in again next week.
And the whole episode ends without her saying a thing.
So why...
Why do I feel so relieved?
I'm the worst.
She's probably so upset right now.
Best try not to bring it up.
Did you watch me last night?
I got a lot of screen time.
She was fine with that?
I guess you were on a bit.
Yamada's got a long way to go before she's a famous actress.
Oh, and here.
What's this?
Can't you tell?
Naoki Suga's signature.
This is fake!
A long, long way.
Why did you even think this would work?
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
初音ミク